[narrator] Heavens Arena.
The 251-story building
which stands 991 meters tall
is a mecca for fighters.
When combatants win a fight,
they may advance by one class,
and receive a corresponding reward.
After reaching the 100th floor,
they are assigned a private room.
And those contestants
who are skilled and fortunate enough
to reach the 200th floor,
earn the right to challenge
the strongest fighters, the Floor Masters,
in an intense battle for survival.
This is, without a doubt,
the best stage a warrior could ask for.
[theme song playing]
[Sadaso]
Today, I’ll beat Killua for my sixth win.
Tomorrow, I'll beat Gon
for my seventh win.
After that
all I’ll need to do
is find three more suckers...
[chuckling]
...then I’ll be a Floor Master!
With the kind of fame and fortune
that’ll get me,
I’ll be set for the rest of my life!
[gasps]
[Killua] You move, you die.
You use Nen and you die.
Make a sound and you die.
If you understand, close your eyes.
Do you see what happens
when you break your promises?
If you do, open your eyes,
look at me in the mirror
and listen carefully.
Don’t ever show your dirty face
in front of us again.
You’ll keep this promise.
POWER x TO x AVENGE
[narrator] There are many who would resort
to using underhanded tactics
to become a Floor Master.
Gon, on the other hand,
has been fiercely concentrating
on improving his Nen
and growing stronger.
And tonight,
he has his battle with Sadaso.
[Sadaso] His eyes…
they belong to someone
who lives in the world of darkness.
I was filled with despair.
I could sense the difference in strength
the second our eyes met.
It was clear that he was the predator
and I was his prey.
It was a huge mistake
to underestimate him.
He isn’t just some normal kid.
I don’t want to die,
so I’m getting the hell out of here.
You should be careful.
He’ll be coming after you guys next!
[disconnected call signal]
[Gido] Now what?
Well, I’m still in.
And I’m willing to do whatever it takes.
I’m almost a Floor Master.
Ten victories on this floor
and you’re allowed
to challenge a Floor Master.
If you win,
you get an entire floor to yourself.
[uneasy grunting]
And as soon as that title is in your hand,
you can lecture, teach, and advise.
Or start up a martial arts school.
For the rest of your life,
you’ve got it made.
[Gido] Do you think that kid’s
gonna come back here to threaten us?
[Riehlvelt]
The boy has no clue what my abilities are.
As long as we’re careful about it,
we should be able
to handle him quite easily.
-[Killua] You're wrong.
-[Riehlvelt and Gido gasp]
It doesn’t really matter
what your abilities are.
[Gido groans]
There’s no rush.
You see… I can always get to you.
Whenever and wherever I want.
At night, when you’re sound asleep
in your bed...
when you’re taking a crap…
Right?
Listen up.
You should follow the rules.
Without the rules,
the only ones benefitting would be us.
[chuckles]
As I was saying:
cheating is a terrible idea.
A fair fight is the way to go.
Right.
[referee] Sadaso’s time is up!
Gon wins by default!
[spectator 1] What? Again?
[spectator 2]
Yeah, what the hell is Sadaso doing?
JUNE 1
JUNE 2
JUNE 3
JUNE 4
[Wing] All right. So today…
Gon will be fighting Gido.
After that, of course,
Killua will be going up against Riehlvelt.
Are you both feeling all right?
[both] Yes sir.
Now, this will be your second match
against Gido,
so I doubt you’ll require much advice.
Have you settled on a strategy?
Yes.
I, uh... think I have.
Well, here’s the thing…
My strategy is to use that.
[Killua] Huh?
Yes, I understand.
[cheering]
[Cocco] The rematch
you’ve all been waiting for
is finally here!
Gido versus Gon!
Their last match landed Gon
in the hospital
but there’s no telling
what we’re in for this time!
For today’s match,
Gon is carrying a fishing rod!
But how exactly does he plan to use it?
Will he be incorporating it
into his fighting style?
Let’s find out!
This is a points and KO system.
No time limit!
Begin!
[Cocco] Right off the bat,
Gon takes off in a mad dash!
But it looks like Gido
was prepared for this!
He’s already responding
with his Tornado Top!
If Gon charges in,
he’ll be in the same position
he was last time!
[Gon] He’s way ahead of me.
[Gido cackling]
[Gido] I know what you’re thinking.
Once I’ve started spinning,
it’s virtually impossible to stop me!
The only logical course would be to hit me
with a preemptive attack
before I even start.
Well, if you’re not going to make a move,
I will!
Shotgun Blues!
SHOTGUN BLUES
He can fire off his tops mid-spin?
[Gido] As you can see,
this technique
is nothing like the Battle Waltz!
All my tops will be aiming right for you!
You’ll never be able to dodge them all!
Ren!
[Gido] What?!
-[audience] Ooh!
-Whoa! He stopped them!
Did you just see that?
Oh, wow…
[Cocco] That was incredible!
Gon just blocked the tops head-on!
He is not the same competitor
he was two months ago!
[Gido] Argh! Damn!
His Nen defenses have shot way up!
Will my tops still be enough to beat him?
[Killua]
Those tops were coming straight at him.
With his reflexes,
Gon could’ve knocked them all down
with his fishing rod.
But he chose to go with Ren instead…
and that did way
more psychological damage to Gido.
He must be thinking about
how they used Zushi to blackmail us...
and he’s furious.
Okay, it’s my turn now!
[Cocco] I wonder what technique
Gon will use this time, folks!
[Gido] He’s using a fishing rod
and that can only mean one thing…
he’ll try to snag my clothes
and bring my spinning to a halt!
But it’s not going to be that easy.
[grunts]
[Cocco] There it is!
He’s going straight for Gido!
[cackling] I knew it.
Not gonna happen!
[Cocco] Oh, no!
His attack missed its target!
[Gido]
[cackling] What were you even aiming at?
[roaring]
What the--?!
[Cocco] Unbelievable!
Gon flipped the floor tile
and Gido along with it!
[screaming]
[groaning]
[yells]
[grunts]
-[roaring]
-No! Wait!
[Cocco] G-- Gon has just broken
Gido’s steel prosthetic leg,
making it very unlikely
that he’ll be able to continue the fight!
[Gon] If you guys resort to any means,
then we won’t hold back, either!
And if you even touch Zushi ever again,
next time I see you,
I’ll break your face in half!
[moaning]
[referee] The winner is... Gon!
[cheering]
[Cocco] Gon was finally able
to avenge his initial loss to Gido!
His record on the 200th floor
is now two to one!
All right. Guess I’m up next.
[Cocco]
And now for the main event of the day…
Killua versus Riehlvelt!
Since Sadaso forfeited the previous match,
this will technically be Killua’s
200th floor debut!
What kind of strategy
are we about to see now?
You do realize
that you broke your promise first.
There’s no way I’ll let you win now.
[Sadaso] His eyes…
they belong to someone
who lives in the world of darkness.
[Riehlvelt] “Someone who lives
in the world of darkness”?
So, what if this brat
is a professional assassin?
Heavens Arena is my turf!
It’s time for me to show him
that within the four sides
of this square stage…
I rule!
Go, Killua! You can do it!
This is a points and KO system!
No time limit!
Begin!
He vanished?
Behind me!
Aura Burst!
AURA BURST
[Cocco]
Riehlvelt boosted out of harm’s way!
He propels his wheelchair
by releasing his stored aura,
guiding it to wherever he wants to go!
I jumped too high.
Whew. That was close.
Two Headed Snake: Twin Serpents!
Song of Defense!
SONG OF DEFENSE
[Cocco] There it is, folks!
Riehlvelt’s Song of Defense!
He protects himself with two whips,
moving at ridiculously high speeds
then waits patiently
for his chance to strike!
[Riehlvelt] You planned to attack first
and take the lead.
Too bad that didn’t work for ya!
Now that I’ve taken this stance,
there is no way you could possibly win!
Why’s that?
[Riehlvelt] It’s obvious, isn’t it?
No normal person on the planet
can keep up with these two whips!
And on this little platform,
there’s nowhere you can run and hide!
[sighs]
Take this!
Yeah? Well, I’m not normal.
Sorry ‘bout that.
[Riehlvelt] What?!
Fine, then.
Thunder Serpent!
[Killua straining]
Hmm...
I’m surprised, Killua!
You’re the first person I’ve fought
who could see my whips in motion!
So, I’ve got a little present for you!
Those two whips together
carry one million volts!
More than enough
to paralyze and incapacitate a giant!
Anyone foolish enough to resist my whips,
will fall victim
to the mighty Thunder Serpent!
[Riehlvelt shrieking]
I’m trained to endure torture,
so electricity won’t work.
It has no effect on me.
I mean, I can tolerate it...
But it isn’t like it makes me happy.
It still really hurts a lot
and everything.
That's why I'm a little pissed.
[crazed chuckle]
[Killua] There’s no way you can survive
a fall from that height.
So, what do you wanna do?
[Riehlvelt]
Catch me! Please! Don’t let me die!
Okay then.
Don’t worry; I’m right here for you!
[frightened cry]
[high-pitched scream of pain]
[crazed chuckle]
[shuddering breath]
Damn it.
At least now you know
how much that hurts, you idiot.
Riehlvelt is down
and so, by virtue of a knockdown,
Killua takes the victory!
[cheering]
[Zushi shouting and laughing]
Nice job, Killua!
[Killua chuckles]
Thanks!
That means you’re up next.
How long ‘til you fight him? Ten days?
Yup. It’ll be on June 10th.
Just remember what worked for me
isn’t gonna work for you, okay?
If those electric whips
so much as touch you,
you’ll be out cold
before you even know what’s happening.
Mm-hmm.
What’s your strategy?
Oh, don’t worry. I think I have an idea.
Oh?
You weren’t watching for nothing, were ya?
Guess you prefer combat to observing, too.
Hmm...
[chuckles quietly]
JUNE 9
[Cocco] It appears that the damage
Gido sustained in his match with Gon
was so severe
that he hasn’t returned for today’s fight.
[referee]
The winner by default is… Killua!
JUNE 10
[Cocco] After losing to Killua,
Riehlvelt’s record is five-three.
He can’t afford another loss!
As you know, after four losses
you’re out of the contest
and have to start over from square one!
He must be wary of Gon’s speed,
because he’s got his whips out already.
Meanwhile, Gon isn’t carrying
his fishing rod.
He’s completely empty-handed!
How does he plan to fight this time?
Begin!
[Cocco]
Song of Defense, right from the start!
Riehlvelt wants to end this fight
in a hurry!
Hmm...
[Cocco] What’s this? Gon is… squatting?
[roaring]
[Cocco] He just ripped up the stone tile
with his bare hands, folks!
-[roars]
-[Cocco] And now he threw it!
[Riehlvelt] Aura Burst!
[Cocco] He escaped in the nick of time!
[Killua]
He left him a way out on purpose….
[Riehlvelt gasps in shock]
[Cocco] But Gon anticipated that move,
and he’s already one step ahead!
[Hisoka]
When you’re trying to escape,
every fraction of a second counts.
And without time to change direction,
all you can do is continue
to move forward.
And accelerating as quickly as that
will throw you off-balance.
His only option at that point
was to stop the whips.
That’s the time to move in!
[screaming in pain]
[wheezing]
So, this is the switch, huh?
Let’s see…
I’ll just turn it up to the max.
No! Stop!
Switch it…
Stop it!
...on!
Just kidding.
Riehlvelt is down!
That counts as a knockout.
The win goes to Gon!
[cheering]
Hey, Gon!
[clapping]
Splendid. Just splendid.
Including your last two matches,
you’ve made progress.
You've made the grade,
so set the time and place
of your choosing.
I’ll take you on any time.
[determined grunt]
[narrator] The strength that Gon
demonstrated in his matches
did not escape Hisoka unnoticed.
It won’t be long now
before their fight begins.
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Coming up:
-Gon...
-[Killua] ...and Killua’s…
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I’m Gon!
-I’m Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we're introducing Cocco.
She announces all of the fights
at Heavens Arena!
Oh. You mean the lady
who’s always talking, huh?
I wonder… how many of her are there?
You think there are mor--?!
[Gon] Next time: “The x True x Pass”!
Killua.
What does ‘so-and-so
and such-and-such’ mean?
[Killua] You really don’t know?
It means "so and so and such and such"!